Hey...
Don't be mad -
What do you think you're doing?!
Put your mask back on!
This was just supposed to be
some anonymous hook up, remember?
Oh wow!
I'm not some bad spirit
that you can just Feng Shui away!
Here.
A blanket and some pillows.
You'll be sleeping on the couch.
Wow!
How very the Hows of Us!
So wait...
I'm Daniel
and you're Kathryn?
We're not Kathniel.
We're not a couple.
And we're not going to have a happy ending.
@alt.media?
What?
Good night.
Maybe we could at least try to start things right.
I dunno.
Try to live in harmony?
Well stop trying.
Hey! Let me in!
I'm sorry!
Rules are rules!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Just make sure the floor isn't wet after.
Yes, Your Majesty.
How could I forget
when there's a huge sign on the door?
[screams]
Shit!
Ah! A ghost!
If this pandemic won't kill me, fear will.
Oh crap.
Hey.
Do you have any extra candles?
What the f -
What the hell are you doing there?!
You really shouldn't sneak up on people in their own houses.
Sorry.
Why are you still up anyway?
And what are you doing in that corner?
Well...
You see...
Oh God.
You're not going to have another panic attack, are you?
No, no, no. I'm okay.
Uhm...
It's just...
Uhhh...
Promise you won't laugh?
It's because...
Uhm...
I'm afraid of the dark.
[laughs]
Hey! You said you wouldn't laugh.
You're too old to be scared of the dark!
You know what?
You're such a bully.
Here.
You can have this.
I think you need this more than I do.
Thank you.
Not too bad for a bully, huh?
Well?
Looks like we're not the only ones without electricity.
There might be a scheduled maintenance.
Most likely, electricity will be back tomorrow.
It's okay.
You're okay.
Who are you talking to?
And...
Do you always have that with you?
This is Kiko.
Really? A stuffed cactus?
Yes!
Because you can't really hug a cactus
without getting hurt.
But I'd like to believe
we all deserve love.
Or at least a proper hug.
Even a cactus.
What a hassle.
It's so hot!
Find the light in the darkness.
At least we're conserving energy?
It's just like Earth Hour.
But for multiple hours...
...and only on this street.
Oh my gosh.
Ugh. Again.
With your brand of toxic positivity.
Not everything is butterflies, glitter, and rainbows.
This is nothing like Earth Hour.
This
is
hell.
Geez!
That's a tad bit overstated.
I'm serious.
Check all the variables.
One, it's awfully hot.
Two, you can't leave.
And three...
Looks like Satan's had it with stirring the pot over the internet.
So he's here right now.
Punishing me.
Wait...
A fallen angel?
Awww!
I know I'm heaven-sent
but for you to really say it warms my heart.
Ha ha! Very funny.
[sighs]
By the way,
Кстати
personal space rules are suspended for now.
Правила личного пространства на время отменены.
It's way too hot in my room.
В моей комнате слишком жарко.
It's like I'm in an oven.
Будто внутри печи.
Wow...
Hypocrite.
Гипокрит.
Again, is this your house?
Повторюсь, это твой дом?
This thing's such a hassle.
Как же надоела эта штука.
What are you doing?
Ты что делаешь?
You're not taking that off.
Нельзя её снимать.
The heat is unbearable
Тут невыносимо жарко.
yet we still need to wear our masks?
Так мы ещё и должны сидеть в маске?
Just look at my mask.
Посмотри на мою маску.
It's soaking wet.
Вся влажная.
I can practically wring the sweat out.
Я буквально могу выжать пот из неё.
I don't care.
Меня не волнует.
You're not the only one who's miserable here.
Не только тебе приходится терпеть тут.
Besides, rules are rules.
К тому же, правила есть правила.
You literally just said rules are suspended.
Ты же только что сказал что правила отменены.
I said personal space rules.
Это было про личное пространство.
I didn't say anything about masks.
Про маски я ничего не говорил.
Fine.
Ладно.
Your wish is my command, Your Majesty.
Ваше слово - закон, ваше величество.
Here you go.
Держи.
So you can fan yourself.
Используй как веер.
Now that we can't see each other
Когда мы не можем видеть друг-друга
maybe we can temporarily take our masks off?
может временно снимем маски?
It's just so hot.
Невыносимо жарко.
Are we good, Your Majesty?
Всё в порядке, ваше величество?
Are you still awake?
Не спишь?
Yeah.
Нет.
Unfortunately.
К сожалению.
We only have seven hours in a day all to ourselves.
У нас есть всего семь часов в день на себя.
Eight to nine hours for work if you're lucky.
От восьми до девяти часов на работу если повезёт.
Then eight hours for sleeping, eating, shitting...
Ещё восемь часов на сон, еду, туалет...
...and all of that.
и всё такое.
So sometimes it's even less than that.
Так иногда выходит даже меньше семи часов.
Huh?
Чего?
You keep poking fun at my positivity, right?
Всё ещё насмехаешься над моей позитивностью, да?
You even said it was toxic.
Даже сказал что она токсичная.
So there.
Итак.
That's the reason why.
Вот и причина.
Why waste such little time we have during the day
Зачем тратить бесценное время на что-то,
being anything but thankful?
кроме того, чтобы быть благодарным.
I guess I just find it weird
Думаю это просто странно,
that the songs you write are all so sad.
что твои песни такие грустные.
Bordering on depressing actually.
На грани депрессии.
Then...
И потом...
...there you are.
ты...
Being all optimistic.
весь оптимистичный.
Yeah.
Да.
Maybe because even if I haven't been in love yet,Может потому что я ещё не был влюблён,
whenever I write,
но когда я пишу,
whether it's painful or sad,
вызывает ли песня грусть или боль,
or even angry,
или даже злость,
I always to go back to why I write in the first place.
Я всегда вспоминаю причину по которой пою.
Love.
Любовь.
And all that comes with it.
И всё, что с ней приходит.
All the pain,
Вся боль,
the anger,
злость,
the failure.
провалы.
That's all a part of it.
Это всё - часть любви.
And in spite of all that
love is persevering.
It's hopeful.
Love is optimistic.
[gags]
Sounds kind of masochistic if you ask me.
I guess that's one way of looking at it.
But our brokenness doesn't mean it's the end.
There's always room to rebuild.
And be whole again.
That's why although my songs may be painful,
I always make sure to end them with hope.
That after everything,
we should never get tired of loving.
That's pretty much it.
And hopefully, through my music,
at least I can reach people.
Help them shout,
cry,
be angry.
All of those things that, because of keeping it all in
they're unable to do.
Because of keeping it all in...
...they're afraid to love again.
How about you?
Have you ever been in love?
Hey!
Well?
Have you ever been in love?
Are you asleep?
Yes. I'm asleep.
[whines]
Come on, tell me!
Have you ever been in love?
[sighs]
I said no personal questions, remember?
Cheater.
We've already broken two rules.
Yes.
Yes?
So you've been in love before?
In fairness.
You know, I didn't expect that from someone who's so glum.
This is why I didn't want any personal questions.
Fine. I'm sorry.
I won't crack jokes anymore.
But hey,
talk to me.
So...what's love like?
What's being in love like?
It's like being exposed to radiation.
It's like you've been smoking for years
or have been exposed to secondhand smoke.
Or like you've been drinking water
without being aware that it had contaminants
like arsenic and chemical carcinogens.
It's a bacterial infection.
It's a parasite.
It's a virus.
If you've heard of Social Cancer,
that's what being in love is like.
It's a silent killer.
It's takes you high up into the heavens
only to drop you nonchalantly out of the sky
without a parachute to help you land safely.
[clears throat]
What now?
That doesn't sound like the love I believe in.
Reality doesn't sound like the love you believe in.
You said so yourself.
Love comes with pain.
It's true.
But more often than not,
there's more pain than happiness.
The bad oftentimes outweighs the good.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Someone must have really hurt you
for your perception of love to be so jaded.
What drove you to make an Alter account?
Were you horny?
Because if you're looking for true love's kiss,
I hate to break it to you,
but you're looking for it in the wrong place.
I told you when we first met, right?
I believe Alter isn't just for physical nudity.
It's a form of self-expression too.
The naked truth.
I guess it started out as a way to gain confidence.
Or at least more than what I already had.
But it eventually became a space
where I could just be me.
The real me.
Without any inhibitions or fear.
What about you?
Uhm...
Me?
I guess...
...for the same reason too.
To gain confidence...
...that I lost.
Confidence that you lost?
Of all the people I know,
you're quite possibly the most sure of himself.
Hey.
For the record,
you don't really know me.
Oh yeah, huh.
We're keeping things anonymous.
You know what?
At some point
relationships really just destroy your confidence.
That's the reality of love.
And it feels like shit.
Especially when you pour your heart and soul
into loving someone.
Someone who you have plans with for how you see your future.
You spent every moment of your life with that person.
And thinking of them.
Just to end up feeling betrayed, angry...embarrassed.
And completely heartbroken.
So much so that you end up questioning yourself.
Questioning your entire being.
Shit.
I had no idea.
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
I'm not trying to be dramatic here.
I'm not looking for sympathy either.
I'm not hungry for validation.
I'm just stating the facts here.
To be frank,
I'm pretty sick of the baggage that comes with relationships.
So the Alter world?
It's the perfect place for me.
All the perks
with no strings attached.
I really think we should take our masks off.
We told each other our nicknames yesterday.
We're already a little less than anonymous, see?
Yieeee!
I only agreed because your Alter handle is a tongue-twister.
So why @alt.media for an Alter handle?
It sounds like a blind item or propaganda account.
You're one to talk.
@trueloveskiss?
Sounds cheesy.
Okay "@alt.media".
At least mine's meaningful.
It actually comes from somewhere.
Your sounds like it's just for kicks.
You know, with a username like that
you should be very careful.
You might end up being attacked by paid troll accounts
with their copy-paste narratives.
I guess I just didn't expect such a common name
for someone who's
famous on Alter.
Maybe I expected something cooler
or something like that.
Don't you like that?
It's still in theme with being anonymous.
It's so common people have trouble tracing me.
I'm sure your parents didn't just name you JM.
Unless...
...they were saving their pen ink?
Doofus.
JM.
Short for John Michael.
Wow!
How unique!
I told you so.
I'm just another face in the crowd.
So there you go.
JM.
John Michael Cruz.
Reb.
Dranreb Medina.